the idea of ​​being alone at en frightens people
独自一人的想法使人们感到恐惧
and that agree that being alone for ever it is necessarily the sawyer bob
并同意永远永远孤单必然是锯工鲍勃（sawyer bob）
position to be a lover be separated formula haar for a while to spent time
成为情人的位置被惯例吵了一会儿，花了一些时间
by yourself and benefit as immensely leds explore the power of solitude
一个人带领自己，并从中受益，探索孤独的力量
[Music] human beings as social creatures
[音乐]人类作为社会生物
nevertheless there are many young beringse for out the ages that shows
但是，有很多年轻人对年龄的追求表明
the left a kind of cherry live anthony the great was one of the desert
剩下一种樱桃活的安东尼，伟大的曾经是沙漠之一
fathers kristin cuff wit group from society to live in the desserts of egypt
来自社会的父亲克里斯汀·库夫（Kristin Cuff）机智小组生活在埃及的甜点中
and follow god de spider seclusion de desert vaders for highly influential
并跟随上帝de Spider隐居de沙漠vaders获得极高的影响力
and the development of four stones since ancient times buddhist monks spent
自古代和尚消亡以来，四块石头的发展
time below some time and someone to deepen their meditation practice and simply
时间低于某个时间，有人会加深他们的冥想练习，简单地
because they know that happiness comes from
因为他们知道幸福来自
begin and that is not require the presence of other people
开始，不需要其他人在场
akkrum society a thousand seen to like looners'
akkrum社会一千被视为喜欢懒惰的人
the heart of toe they cannot stand man participation people at prefer being
他们无法忍受男人参与的脚趾心，人们更喜欢被
alone seem to info suspicion first there or if you'd like she must be
独自一人似乎首先要引起人们的怀疑，或者您是否想让她一定要
crazy person or no one like share them there is the preparing je terrorist
疯狂的人或没有人喜欢分享他们，那里有正在准备的恐怖分子
attack koutoubia serial killer or maybe you
攻击库图比亚连环杀手，也许你
which in popular culture phil is a soft and who picks it up
在流行文化中，菲尔是软的，谁接了它
solitary creatures column of lord of the rings
指环王的独生生物专栏
batman's choker and smurfs' gargamel so just that really mean
蝙蝠侠的cho子和蓝精灵的gargamel，所以这真的意味着
that solitude is bad for you know that all
孤独对你不利，你知道所有
solitude champion blessing and science s trials that spending time alone can
独处冠军的祝福和科学的考验，光是消磨时光就可以
hefter mendez benefits of use my soul ii soul het ud cambier powerful tool for
hefter mendez使用我的灵魂的好处ii het ud cambier的强大工具
achieving half happiness and success biological great opportunity for
实现一半的幸福和成功，生物的巨大机会
reflection by reflecting onlive weekend find out what
通过反思生活的周末来反思，找出什么
direction to go and what you or ever want a future
前进的方向以及您或曾经想要的未来
instead of learning through life like a headless chicken
而不是像无头的鸡一样终生学习
week schedule hair and make-up butts decision to close shirt and through and open
每周安排头发和彩妆的决定，以关闭衬衫并贯穿并打开
now want and wife created a game plan it's time for the execution another
现在想要和妻子制定了一个游戏计划，是时候执行另一个了
power of solitude is productivity where we spent time alone were less
孤独的力量是生产力，我们独自度过的时间更少
likely to be distracted by other people of course, it is essential that we don't
可能会被其他人分心，我们必须不要
replays young interaction with old distractions
重播年轻人与旧事物的互动
like binge-watching 'series on netflix swipe left and right on dating apps and
就像netflix上的观看狂欢系列一样，在约会应用上向左和向右滑动，
the endless rabbit hole of i-clips en frans showing gets for
i-clips en frans的无尽兔子洞显示为
lunch and social media if you want to be productive in solitude
午餐和社交媒体，如果您想独享生产力
you might want to consider cutting edge of time spent on the internet
您可能要考虑节省在互联网上花费的时间
that activation or facebook account and flow your smartphone into the river
激活或Facebook帐户，并将您的智能手机流入河流
if you are down, you're ready to accomplish the great things you do
如果您情绪低落，则准备好完成自己所做的伟大工作
dream wolf like nikola tesla tesla was a lifelong
像尼古拉·特斯拉（Nikola tesla）一样的梦狼特斯拉（Tesla）终生
bachelor and the old days with and that meet great contribution to the
学士学位以及与的过去，对
world to optimize creativity i secluded m itself resulting in a razor sharp
优化创造力的世界我与世隔绝，导致剃刀锋利
focus many artists and offers spent time away
吸引许多艺术家，并提供花费的时间
from the noisy society to work under project pablo picasso's side and a
从嘈杂的社会到帕勃罗·毕加索（Pablo Picasso）的项目下工作，
quote we would work as great solitude no-show
引用我们将非常孤独地出现
possible and quote solitude thousand just benefit performance as if brushing
可能，并且报价孤独1000只会像刷牙一样使性能受益
meaning and position to explore and just a brace or even meditation is an ancient one
进行探索的意义和位置，只是大括号甚至是冥想都是古老的
practice in knew how absurd nathalia mistake causing emotions and fiscal
在实践中知道纳塔利人的荒谬错误会导致情绪和财务上的混乱
sensations and both at serving her cells to find out what's going on in
的感觉，并在服务她的细胞，以找出正在发生的事情
your body and might insight in or even helps to make better
您的身体，可能会洞察甚至帮助您做得更好
life decisions is how you learn to work with your
人生的决定就是你学会与自己合作的方式
own company who become less dependent on other young bx
自己对其他年轻bx的依赖减少的公司
some people hefter tendency to your parents and taft and towns
有些人倾向于你的父母，塔夫脱和城镇
I linked people that aren't good company to my new lay's chips ar de
我把不好的人与我的新手芯片联系起来
street with people stay in men your closet dough falls further or being alone
与人呆在街上的男人，你的衣柜里的面团会掉得更远，或者一个人呆着
at your content being where you yourself is easy to wow from people that aren't
在您满意的地方，您很容易就被那些不属于自己的人所惊叹
gujarat and overlooked a lot further it will you it is the opportunity to
古吉拉特邦，并进一步忽略了它，这将是您的机会
cultivate love this may sound a bit strange is how you season with
培养爱情，这听起来可能有点奇怪，这是你如何适应
cultivating life can only be done by interaction the kia is that we have it for years
培养生命只能通过互动来完成。起亚是我们拥有多年
pay how poor spending time with a shirt and
付钱花多长时​​间花在一件衬衫上
group of friends marco burgers which makes it free of
群的朋友马可汉堡，使它摆脱了
england preferences in solitude were able to see the big picture and culture
英国人对孤独的喜好能够看到全局和文化
love for much wider range of people and common practice to the Buddhist
对佛教徒的热爱和佛教徒的常识
is meta meditation which i fox loving kindness
是我对爱的善意的元冥想
then ward will be boeings in the universe so if you want to be more compassionate with
那么病房将成为宇宙中的波音，所以如果您想更富有同情心
loving products and game more insight into yourself concealer harvesting the power of
喜爱产品和游戏的人可以更深入地了解自己的遮瑕膏，从而收获遮盖力
solitude tank full of what you
孤独的坦克充满了你
[Music]
[音乐]